businessnews24hr.com 2012-04-13

# Terms of Use and Privacy Notice

**Privacy Statement**

We do not collect any personal information when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us. If you choose to provide us with personal information by sending an e-mail to us, or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it through our website, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us get the information you have requested. We do not collect personal information for any other purposes. Moreover, we do not create individual profiles with the information you provide or give this information to any private organizations. We would share your e-mail only if required to do so by law.

Our website may use session cookies for technical purposes such as to enable better navigation through the site, or to allow you to customize your preferences for interacting with the site. At no time is your private information, whether stored in persistent cookies or elsewhere, shared with third parties who have no right to that information. 

**Disclaimer**

We may link to external sites that help us perform our mission or illustrate news reports. Links to external servers do not imply any official endorsement of the opinions or ideas expressed therein, nor do such links guarantee the validity of the information provided. Links to commercial sites are in no way an endorsement of any vendor's products or services.  

The writers have to agree to clause that they will not infringe copy write material. If any such article is brought our notice, we will act in accordance the following copy write policy.  
Users indemnify and hold harmless businessnews24.com, its partners and sponsors in issues related to content submitted.  

All submitters have to attest that they have or have obtained ownership/rights/permissions necessary to legally distribute the content. Further, content submitters accept complete liability for their submission; fully attesting to the fact there is no illegal content and they alone are responsible for any claims to the contrary. Any information, comments and stories posted to this site include the user's real name.  

The articles carry opinion of respective authors, businessnews24hr.com do not endorse or subscribe to their opinion. If any inaccurate, malicious story is brought to our notice, we will immediately delete it. Please inform us at: [tina.joseph@media24hr.com](mailto:tina.joseph@media24hr.com)

Rules for Posting Comments

 All comments will be reviewed before posting. We will make every effort to review and post comments. If any objectionable comments is published due to oversight, please bring us to our notice and we promise immediate action. All comments must follow these rules: 

 1\. Stay on topic. 

2\. No obscenity, profanity, vulgarity, hate language, SHOUTING, or other bad behavior. 

3\. No personal attacks. No inflammatory language or calls for violence.

4\. Simple text only, please.No html or other code. 

**Copyright Statement**

We respect the intellectual property of others, and we ask users of the businessnews24hr.com to do the same. We have adopted a policy that provides for the termination in appropriate circumstances of account holders who infringe the rights of copyright holders. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please send all relevant details to us at: [tina.joseph@media24hr.com](mailto:tina.joseph@media24hr.com)

This is a brief summary of terms of use and privacy notice. For detailed exhaustive document, please contact [ tina.joseph@media24hr.com](mailto:tina.joseph@media24hr.com) .
